American Council for Polish Culture Collection. 1940-2013 CPAA 96-03
Connecticut Polish American Archives, Elihu Burritt Library, Central Connecticut State University, New Britain
- Inventory
  - ACPC - Archives Correspondence Committee Pt. 1, 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - ACPC - Archives Correspondence Committee Pt. II, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - ACPC - Correspondence of ACPC Archives Related to Prospective Repository, 1994-1998 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - ACPC - Archive Repository Search, 1992,1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - ACPC - 2 Photos- Gregory Biestek presenting the A.C.P.C collection to Prof Blejwas, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - ACPC - Convention Notes, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - ACPC - Convention- Membership Material, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - ACPC - Convention- Souvenir Pamphlet, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - ACPC - Annual Convention booklet, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - ACPC - Convention- Membership Material, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - ACPC - Convention Reports Booklet, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - ACPC - Convention- Minutes, Motions, Financial, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - ACPC - Convention Reports, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - ACPC - Spring Board Meeting, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - ACPC - Fall Board Meeting, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - ACPC - Spring Board Meeting, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - ACPC - Fall Board Meeting, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - ACPC - Spring Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - ACPC - Fall Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - ACPC - Summer Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - ACPC - Fall Board Meeting, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - ACPC - Fall Board Meeting, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - ACPC - Spring Board Meeting, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - ACPC - Fall Board Meeting, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - ACPC - Spring Board Meeting, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - ACPC - Fall Board Meeting Pt.I, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - ACPC - Fall Board Meeting Pt.II, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - ACPC - Spring Board Meeting, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - ACPC - Youth Leadership Conference Reports, 2002,2003 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - ACPC - Youth Leadership Conference- Applications, Donations, Expenses, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - ACPC - Youth Leadership Conference 7th National Program, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - ACPC - Youth Leadership Conference- Participants, Cost, Program + Clippings (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - ACPC - Youth Leadership Conference- Applicants, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - ACPC - Youth Leadership Conference- Correspondence Donations, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - ACPC - Youth Leadership Conference- Bank Statements, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - ACPC - Youth Leadership Conference - Program, List of Participants, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - ACPC - Youth Leadership Conference- Bank Statements, 2003-2013 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - ACPC - Letter from the Treasurer to CCSU Archives, May 20, 2013 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - ACPC - Annual Convention Photos, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - ACPC - Food Drive Photographs, "Solidarity Express", 1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - ACPC - Photographs of Board Meeting, Orlando, FL, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - ACPC - Polish American Historical Association award recipient Dr. Stanislaw A. Blejwas and Angela Pienkos, 1980, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - ACPC - Photographs used for Polish Heritage publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - ACPC - Photographs from conventions by Alfred F. Bochenek, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - ACPC - Resolution to Establish the Thaddeus Kosciuszko House in Philadelphia, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - ACPC - The Polish Arts and Culture Foundation popular publication on Poland's traditions (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - ACPC - Our Second Quarter Century 1973-1998, The History of the ACPC, by Anna Chrypinska (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - ACPC - 58th Annual Convention, Gdansk, Poland, July 11-16, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - ACPC - 60th Annual Convention, Jamestown, Virginia, August 6-10, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - ACPC - 62nd Annual Convention, Rapid City, South Dakota, July 14-17, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - ACPC - 63rd Annual Convention, Cleveland, Ohio, July 14-17, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - ACPC - 64th Annual Convention, Williamsburg, Virginia, July 18-21, 2012 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - ACPC - 65th Annual Convention, Baltimore, Maryland, July 31-August 4, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - ACPC - 5 VHS tapes from 43rd Annual Convention in Pultusk, Poland, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - ACPC - Binders with materials and photographs covering activities and annual conventions, 1991, 1992, 1995, 1998, 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - ACPC - Binders with materials and photographs covering activities and annual conventions, 2003-2007 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - ACPC - Binders with materials and photographs covering activities and annual conventions, 2008-2013 (Box 23, Folder 1)